[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question": "How is the kanji '風邪' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "かぜ"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question": "How is the kanji '出張' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "しゅっちょう"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question": "How is the kanji '出張します' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "しゅっちょうします"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question": "How is the kanji 'お大事に' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "おだいじ"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question": "How is the kanji '飛びます' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "とびます"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question": "How is the kanji '運びます' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "はこびます"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question": "How is the kanji '戻します' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "もどします"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question": "How is the kanji '星' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "ほし"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question": "How is the kanji '光' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "ひかり"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "How is the kanji '空' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "そら"
    },
    {
        "id": "11",
        "question": "How is the kanji '音' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "おと"
    }
]